railyatri.in 2016-06-17

# RailYatri.in | Privacy Policy

  * Policy

We appreciate & value the trust that you have placed on us.Our privacy policy demonstrates our commitment to the privacy of the users for our Site (www.railyatri.in and its allied sites) and RailYatri App ( RailYatri Android app, iOS app , Windows app & any other product owned by RailYatri). Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

Please note that by visiting this Site or using RailYatri App you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy which is a legally binding agreement between you and us, Stelling Technologies Pvt. Ltd., the owner of the Site & RailYatri App ("Company"). If you do not agree, please do not use or access this Site or RailYatri App. By mere use or access of the Site or RailYatri App, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. 

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time, without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, kindly review this policy periodically. 

  * What this Privacy Policy Covers?

This privacy policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information collected by this Site and RailYatri App. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of entities that the Company does not own or control, or of persons that the Company does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which this Site links. 

  * Collection and Use of Personal Information

    * You can visit the Site without revealing any personal information. However, once you register yourself to avail our services, you will be sharing your personal information with us. This helps us provide you a safe and customized experience on our site. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Site. 
    * While using RailYatri Android app or any other RailYatri App, we may collect & store your email address, phone number & SMS pertaining to your train travel in order to help us communicate and to inform you with status updates and to keep you informed. We may automatically track certain information about you, like GPS location & others based upon your behavior on RailYatri App. 
    * This information may be used for internal analysis on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior patterns to help us better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the source URL, destination URL, your operating system, device, browser information, and your IP address. We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties 
    * If you choose to transact on the Site or the RailYatri App, we may collect information about your transaction behavior, such as your mobile number, billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details. Social Web Information. This includes but limited to your Facebook connect credentials (and information that you authorize Facebook share with us though permissions and email account information. If you authorize and provide it to us, we may also collect information concerning e-mail contacts and other social web information. To help you connect friends and contacts you may want to use our service with (as well as to improve or services and fight fraud), we may also allow you to import data from other social web services. If you choose to post content on our Site or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site or RailYatri App, we may collect 

  * Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information to third parties who work with us to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information We may otherwise disclose your personal information when: We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our Site or defend the rights or property; We find that your actions on our Sites violate the Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

  * RailYatri Android App Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Stelling Technologies Private Limited (“RailYatri”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the RailYatri Android Application or your mobile phone. RailYatri android app collects and uses information as described in "Collection and Use of Personal Information" section. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. The terms "we", "us", and “our website” refer to RailYatri Android App or [www.railyatri.in](http://www.railyatri.in/) and the terms "you" and "your" refer to you, as a user of one of our services. The term "personal information" means information that you provide to us which personally identifies you to be contacted or identified, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information. 

  * Information Collection and Use

RailYatri.in uses information we collect to analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track User Content and users as necessary to comply with the Copyright and Information Act, Information Technology Act, and other applicable laws of India. 

  * User-Provided Information

When you install and start using the RailYatri Android app on your mobile, you may provide us information about yourself, such as your e-mail address, basic information about your phone's operating system and other information that you grant us access to depending on the permissions settings within the application. We do not sell or provide this information to any third party (companies, individuals or websites) and user all standard technology procedures to safeguard your information. When you search for a specific train, station or any such travel information using the app, we may collect certain metadata (i.e when it was searched, how many times it was searched etc.) but we do not collect any information that can associate such information with you as a user or your travel plans. 

  * Information Collected Automatically

When you use the app, we may use certain tracking technologies to: (a) store your username, password and authentication tokens; (b) analyze the usage of the Service; (c) customize the Service to your preferences; and (d) control the advertising displayed by the Service. Some features of the app are dependent on the location the user is present at the moment when the app is being used. However, this information is only used to provide a more contextual and personalized experience and is no way used to track the user. We may use these automated technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information we consider to be non-personal information, including: (a) information related to the devices you use to access or interact with the Service, such as: geolocation information, unique device identifiers and other information about your mobile phone or other mobile device(s). Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) may allow third parties to serve advertisements on the application and on third-party services and use other third parties to help us collect and analyze information about your use of the service, generate aggregate site usage statistics and provide content sharing services to support the Service. These third parties may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect similar non-personal information about your use of the Service. We do not control the third parties' use of such technologies and their use is governed by those parties'privacy policies. 

  * How We Share Your Information

Personally Identifiable Information: Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) may share your personally identifiable information with affiliates for the purpose of providing the Service to you or with affiliates offering combined services with us. If we do this, such affiliates use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside our direct control (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as if you choose to sign on to the Service through a third-party service. We cannot control affiliates use of your information. Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or summon or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect our rights or property. 

  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may aggregate and/or anonymize information collected through the Service so that the information does not identify you. We may use aggregated, anonymized, and other non-personally identifiable information for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and our use and disclosure of such information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy. Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service and on third-party services. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on our property. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The Stelling Technolgoies (RailYatri) PrivacyPolicy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information. 

  * Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, emailaddress, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

  * Consent

By using the Site and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy. 

  * Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. 

  * Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of this Site after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

  * Grievance Officer

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below - **Mr. Dinesh Rathi** **Stelling Technologies Private Limited** **A-5,6,7 1st Floor, Amco Tower,** **Amaltash Marg, A Block, Sector 9,** **Noida 201301** **U.P., India** **Email: dinesh.rathi@stellingtech.com** **Questions or Suggestions** If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at feedback@railyatri.in.
